<news>

<newsitem headline="Enjoy my work?">
<text>Please take the time to rate GSD Mobile on Google Play and share it with friends that may like my work. Im expanding my horizons in 2017 to increase popularity, revenue and knowledge. Bigger and better things are in the horizon.  </text>
<date>29 September 2016</date>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Slab">
<text>Based on Sapphire Launcher's Dashclock Panel feature, Slab is a new dashclock management app set to release in 2017 for Android 6.0+ More information as it becomes available. It will also be an add-on for Project Niebieski. </text>
<date>29 September 2016</date>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="GSD Maintenance">
<text>GocalSD will be going under maintenance this weekend. If visiting the domain and you experience a slow connection or buggy behavior, that is the culpret and not your internet provider or neighbors wifi. These changes is for a new update expexted for GSD Mobile soon regarding the newsfeed. </text>
<date>29 September 2016</date>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Sapphire's Fall Update">
<text>The new launcher update is expected to drop in October with a variety of interface changes and enhancements for Android N and bugs fixes that have been tracked since discovery. Stay tuned to GSD. </text>
<date>27 September 2016</date>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Nx Certificates">
<text>The Sapphire Launcher license keys will be updated soon to be universal keys for future projects. They will also be renamed Nx certificates based on their class. This will not affect Sapphire Launcher users in any way but will affect any users who simply installed the APKs without purchasing them. A licensed verification will be made and I will be notified of who isn't using a verified key. This will be logged in the Google dev console. Your device will be logged simply, nothing more unless you have a past history of purchases with me or returns. </text>
<date>23 September 2016</date>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Niebieski Information services">
<text>New information about the launcher project going into development soon is surfacing on GSD. Sapphyx Launcher will put the hammer down for performance and reliability for a launcher desktop in Android N with custom performance drivers, a hybrid key registry and more expansion based enhancements. </text>
<date>17 September 2016</date>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Game with the dev!">
<text>Hit me up on PS4 Dracos_Aura or Windows10 Live GT Dracos Aura</text>
<date>13 September 2016</date>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Prism Assistant">
<text>A new update will be releasing for Prism Assistant. This update brings a new interface, a few new bug fixes for Android N and... It will become a free application and bring un-intrusive ads.</text>
<date>17 September 2016</date>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="2017 Expected Roadmap">
<text>Several new apps are in development for GSD to release in 2017 and several major updates for legacy apps. A wide range of new tools, utilities and methods will be used to develop the new gen release of apps using 64bit technology and compilers. A great learning process. </text>
<date>13 September 2016</date>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="System76 Kudo Donation">
<text>Recent development is of need of a more powerful workspace. I am currently investing Onyx keys and Ads revenue towards a System 76 Kudo for Android development. If you'd like to donate to this, you may send a small donation to my gmail via Google Wallet. Recent updates Via windows10 have corrupted my ability to manage a dual boot system of Ubuntu and Windows and risking valuable information and data isnt apart of my game plan. </text>
<date>8 September 2016</date>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Welcome to the Newsfeed!">
<text>You'll find current events, announcments, blog summaries, project exclusive info and more here!</text>
<date>7 September 2016</date>
</newsitem>

</news>
