<news>

<newsitem headline="2017 Expected Roadmap">
<text>Several new apps are in development for GSD to release in 2017 and several major updates for legacy apps. A wide range of new tools, utilities and methods will be used to develop the new gen release of apps using 64bit technology and compilers. A great learning process. </text>
<date>13 September 2016</date>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Sapphire Launcher 11.4">
<text>The newest update is available via Google Play and XDA Labs. Preparation for translations are almost here. One issue is being tracked with the dark statusbar as it borks the widget container when activated but doesn't affect anything else. A fix is being investigated. Simply deactivate the tweak if errors accure. Please report the problem via Bug report feature or the google plus group. </text>
<date>12 September 2016</date>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Sapphire License Keys">
<text>An October scheduled updated will allow Sapphire Launcher License keys to be universal on both Sapphire Launcher and Sapphyx Launcher. This update will add license verification via google play purchases and a universal name to not confuse new and legacy customers. Onyx keys will be verified upon Early Access for Sapphyx Launcher.</text>
<date>8 September 2016</date>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Kudos Donation">
<text>Recent development is of need of a more powerful workspace. I am currently investing Onyx keys and Ads revenue towards a System 76 Kudos for Android development. If you'd like to donate to this, you may send a small donation to my gmail via Google Wallet. Recent updates Via windows10 have corrupted my ability to manage a dual boot system of Ubuntu and Windows and risking valuable information and data isnt apart of my game plan. </text>
<date>8 September 2016</date>
</newsitem>
  
<newsitem headline="We're live!">
<text>GSD Mobile is now live!</text>
<date>7 September 2016</date>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Welcome to the Newsfeed!">
<text>You'll find current events, announcments, blog summaries, project exclusive info and more here! Expect more as we get settled down.</text>
<date>7 September 2016</date>
</newsitem>

</news>
