<news>

<newsitem headline="Nx Certificates">
<text>The Sapphire Launcher license keys will be updated soon to be universal keys for future projects. They will also be renamed Nx certificates based on their class. This will not affect Sapphire Launcher users in any way but will affect any users who simply installed the APKs without purchasing them. A licensed verification will be made and I will be notified of who isn't using a verified key. This will be logged in the Google dev console. Your device will be logged simply, nothing more unless you have a past history of purchases with me or returns. </text>
<date>23 September 2016</date>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Dew Companion">
<text>Halo Online Eldewrito Mod is my target in my next small project. A companion application will be developed for Halo PC players to find and navigate through information easily and target specific threads on Reddit,community content and software updates and more. Stay tuned for more information and a Vidoc explaining the purpose of the project and why inwish to support this project. </text>
<date>17 September 2016</date>

</newsitem>
<newsitem headline="Niebieski Information services">
<text>New information about the launcher project going into development soon is servicing on GSD. Sapphyx Launcher will put the hammer down for performance and reliability for a launcher desktop in Android N with custom performance drivers, a hybrid key registry and more expansion based enhancements. </text>
<date>17 September 2016</date>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Game with the dev!">
<text>Hit me up on PS4 Dracos_Aura or Windows10 Live GT Dracos Aura</text>
<date>13 September 2016</date>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Prism Assistant">
<text>A new update will be releasing for Prism Assistant. This update brings a new interface, a few new bug fixes for Android N and... It will become a free application and bring un-intrusive ads.</text>
<date>17 September 2016</date>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="2017 Expected Roadmap">
<text>Several new apps are in development for GSD to release in 2017 and several major updates for legacy apps. A wide range of new tools, utilities and methods will be used to develop the new gen release of apps using 64bit technology and compilers. A great learning process. </text>
<date>13 September 2016</date>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Sapphire License Keys">
<text>An October scheduled updated will allow Sapphire Launcher License keys to be universal on both Sapphire Launcher and Sapphyx Launcher. This update will add license verification via google play purchases and a universal name to not confuse new and legacy customers. Onyx keys will be verified upon Early Access for Sapphyx Launcher.</text>
<date>8 September 2016</date>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Kudos Donation">
<text>Recent development is of need of a more powerful workspace. I am currently investing Onyx keys and Ads revenue towards a System 76 Kudos for Android development. If you'd like to donate to this, you may send a small donation to my gmail via Google Wallet. Recent updates Via windows10 have corrupted my ability to manage a dual boot system of Ubuntu and Windows and risking valuable information and data isnt apart of my game plan. </text>
<date>8 September 2016</date>
</newsitem>
  
<newsitem headline="We're live!">
<text>GSD Mobile is now live!</text>
<date>7 September 2016</date>
</newsitem>

<newsitem headline="Welcome to the Newsfeed!">
<text>You'll find current events, announcments, blog summaries, project exclusive info and more here! Expect more as we get settled down.</text>
<date>7 September 2016</date>
</newsitem>

</news>
